Sergiy Kochenko - Junior Full Stack Developer

Tralee, County Kerry, Ireland



sergiykochenko@gmail.com



+353 873407890



linkedin.com/in/sergiy-kochenko-a93a30135



https://github.com/SergiyKochenko

Summary

Junior Software Developer with a Diploma in Full-stack Software Development from the Code Institute. Proficient in HTML, CSS, Javascript, and Python3. I have 15 years of experience in Maritime Service. I am a valuable team player with strong communication skills and effective problem-solving abilities. I am eager to gain entry into the tech industry into an exciting development team where I can grow and contribute!

Experience



QA/QC Engineer

Ubertesters

Apr 2022 - Present (1 year 3 months)

IT methodologies, test cases, checklists, defect management, testing strategies and approaches, test levels, requirements analysis, performance testing, databases

Deck Officer

V. Ships

Aug 2006 - Feb 2022 (15 years 7 months)

- Deck Cadet
- 3rd Officer
- 2nd Officer
- Chief Officer

Deck hand

V.Ships

Jul 2001 - Aug 2006 (5 years 2 months)

- Utility Store
- Dishwasher
- Ordinary Seamen
- Able Seamen

Education



Code Institute

Bachelor's degree, Full Stack Software Development (E-commerce Applications)

Nov 2022 - May 2023

Diploma in Full Stack Software Development (E-commerce Applications)

Code Institute's Diploma in Full Stack Software Development is an intense and rewarding programme created and validated by tech industry experts and academics.

Online University "TOMMY"

Diploma of QA/QC Engineer, IT

Feb 2022 - Apr 2022

IT methodologies, test cases, checklists, defect management, testing strategies and approaches, test levels, requirements analysis, performance testing, and databases.

National University "Odessa Maritime Academy"

Diploma of Bachelor's degree, Marine Transportation Sep 2008 - Jun 2012

I.O. Marinesko Odessa Maritime - College - Odessa, Ukraine

Diploma of Junior Specialist, Marine Transportation Sep 2003 - Jul 2006

I.O. Marinesko Odessa Maritime - College - Odessa, Ukraine

Diploma of Junior Specialist, Transportation and Logistics Management Sep 1996 - Jul 1999

Licenses & Certifications

- Certified Associate in Software Testing (CAST) TOMMY On Line University
- **5 Day Coding Challenge** Code Institute
- O Diploma in Full Stack Software Development (E-commerce Applications) Code Institute

Skills

Full Stack Software Development | Python3 | Django | JavaScript ES6 | jQuery | PostdreSQL | AWS | eCommerce | Stripe | CSS3 | Bootstrap | HTML5

My Portfolio projects:

Project 5 eCommerce

Technologies Used - HTML5 , CSS, Python3, JavaScript and Unit test.

GitHub Repo - https://github.com/SergiyKochenko/pp5-house-stock-ecommerce

Live Site - https://pp5-house-stock-ecommerce.herokuapp.com/

Project 4

Technologies Used - HTML5, CSS, Python3, JavaScript and Unit test. GitHub Repo - https://github.com/SergiyKochenko/portfolio-project-four Live Site - https://app-portfolio-project-four.herokuapp.com/

Project 3

Technologies Used - HTML5 , CSS and Python3. GitHub Repo - https://github.com/SergiyKochenko/atm-bunking-app Live Site - https://atm-bunkinng-app.herokuapp.com/

Project 2

Technologies Used - HTML5 , CSS and JavaScript. GitHub Repo - https://github.com/SergiyKochenko/ProjectTwo Live Site - https://sergiykochenko.github.io/ProjectTwo/

Project 1

Technologies Used - HTML5 and CSS.

GitHub Repo - https://github.com/SergiyKochenko/SergiyKochenko
Live Site - https://sergiykochenko.github.io/SergiyKochenko/